EM CHANTHOU

Address: Taley Village, Street Lom, Sangkat Cherng Ek,

Khan Dong Kao, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

Tel. (+855) 96 215 0690

Email: chanthouem690@gmail.com



OBJECTIVE

Position as Accountant

Dear Hiring Manager

2014 - 2015

According to your job announcement to seek qualified candidates for the position of **Accountant** at **Cambodia Airport Investment Co, Ltd.**, I'm so interested in it. With my real capacity and plentiful experience I think I'm suitable to hold this position in your company. So I would like to present my CV for your consideration.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Nationality : Cambodian

Sex : Female

Marital Status : Single

Health : Excellence

Date of Birth : July 27th, 1996

Place of Birth : Beong Tranh, South Beong Tranh, Samrong, Takeo, Cambodia

PERSONAL QUALITIES

_	Able to communicate in Knmer, English
	Able to work in group and individual
	Good communication and interpersonal skill
	Able to learn, adopt and improve quickly
	Proactive, challenge and creative idea to solve the problems
	Self-confidence and high responsibility and commitment

WORKING EXPERIENCES

2017 - Present	:	Working as Accountant and Administration at EPS Security Co., Ltd.
2017 - 2018	:	Working as Accountant at Sun Bight Infinite
2015 - 2017	:	Working as Marketing and Call Center at New Day Technology
2014 - 2015	:	Working as Accountant at ASC Security

: Working as Chef Assistant a Restaurant

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

□ 2017 - 2020 : Vanda Institute of Accounting (Graduated)

□ 2014 - 2017 : Bachelor degree of Accounting (BBA) at Cambodia Accounting and

□ Law Institute

□ 2012 - 2014 : High School at Hun Sen Angprey Takeo Province

□ 2008 - 2011 : Secondary Hun Sen Angprey High School Takeo Province

TRAINING AND COURSES

☐ Jan - Present : Study English Starting skills at Cambodia Accounting and Law Institute

□ 2013 - 2014 : training at YCC

LANGUAGES AND COMPUTER

Khmer : Mother Tongue

English : Listening, reading, speaking and writing (Good)

Computer : Microsoft Word, Excel, QuickBooks, PowerPoint, Google search engine

HABIT

☐ Watching TV, Reading books, Magazine, newspapers, Listening music

☐ Strong willingness to learn and apply ideas

Researching new important knowledge to improve skill and I'm also a keen traveler and enjoy photography.

REFERENCE

➤ Ms. EM TINA

o Position : Accountant at Java Café & Gallery

o Tel. : (+855) 15 633 477

➤ Mr. MOL PUTHY

Position : Senior Backend System Developer at Wing (Cambodia) Limited

Specialised Bank

• Tel. : (+855) 96 527 0842